"以法之名" 前情提要...
Previously on damages...
谋杀武器上 发现沾有她未婚夫
血迹的她的血指纹
We found her prints and her
fianc?s blood on the murder weapon.
Ellen Parsons
你涉嫌谋杀David Connor 现在被捕
Ellen parsons,you're under arrest
for the murder of david connor.
Hollis Nye说你想见我
Hollis nye said you wanted to see me.
我要你帮我找到Patty
I need you to find patty.
没人知道她在哪里
Nobody knows where she is.
Nye先生 Tom刚走
Mr.Nye,tom just left.
跟着他
Stay on him.
他会带你找到Patty
He'll lead you to patty.
我们头一次争吵
We had our first fight.
你和David需要多些相处的时间
你们都太忙了
You and david need to take some
time together. You're both so busy.
他们都是勤劳善良的人
害怕失去你
They're good,hardworking people,and
they're afraid of losing you.
你努力树立典范
You try to lead by example.
他们希望你来指引
却又为此而不满
And they want you to lead,and
then they resent you for it.
看来我们的Gregory Malina
最终还是要上庭作证
Looks like our boy gregory malina's
going to be deposed after all.
我不会让你朋友面对Patty Hewes
经受盘问
I am not going to let your young friend sit across
a table from patty hewes and face an inquisition.
你的证人看来有更重要的事
Your witness has other priorities.
他跑了
I lost him.
去找到他
Then find him.
我和你一起可以解决这件事
I think that you and I
together could end this.
我们坚持自己的计划
Let's stick to our plan.
拿钱 继续过生活
Take this money and
get on with our lives.
你的合作很有价值
Your cooperation has been invaluable.
我要付你双倍酬劳
I want to double our arrangement.
你还没配新钥匙
You still didn't make new keys.
没时间
Oh,there's no time.
- 你姐说会把多配的一副拿过来
- 她没拿来
- Your sister was going to bring over the extra set
- but She didn'T.
对不起 David...
I'm so ...
这是什么?
Whoa,what is this?
做蛋糕的把结婚蛋糕送来了
The cake lady sent them
over for the wedding.
要我们选?
We have to choose?
但我得走了 你选什么我都行...
不要柠檬味太重就好
But I gotta go,so whatever you like is
great with me-- just nothing too lemony.
等等 不! 我不选
Wait.No,no!I'm not deciding.
为什么?
Why not?
我是男人 我才不管这些
Because I'm the guy.
I don't give a shit.
好吧 有道理
Okay,fine,fair enough.
这个 很棒
Oh,this one. It's great.
David!
你在David生前最后一次见他
****
你俩怎么了
What happened*******
David和我...
David and I had...
慢慢说
Take your time.
David和我吵架了
David and I had a fight.
我已经不知道你在做什么了
I don't know what you're doing anymore.
我知道自己在做什么
I know exactly what I'm doing.
是吗? 已经有个人死了
Oh,really? A man's dead now.
那也是计划中的?
Was that the plan?
这是代价
This is what it takes.
我不想要这样的生活
I don't want this life.
你现在决定...要我们在一起
还是要这份工作?
You decide right now-- do you
want us or do you want this job?
- 别这样
- 马上决定
- Please don't do this.
- Right now.
现...在!
Right... now!
你没法决定 对吗?
You can't decide,can you?
David?
不
No. No.
我们完了 Ellen
We're done,ellen.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-=YTET-伊甸园&CHD联盟字幕组=-
时间轴: 咔肉肉 调整 捕头@CHD联盟
翻译: elise 小乔 silvierun
校对: sade
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:咔肉肉
以法之名
第一季 第8集
Damages
Season01 Episode08
- 再见 Michael
- 再见 妈
Bye,michael. Bye,mom.
一年来第一次一家人吃早餐
First family breakfast in over a year.
我们找不到Gregory Malina
We can't find gregory malina.
Patty?
怎么了 Tom?
What,tom?
有法院指令要Gregory出现
There's a court order
for gregory to appear.
没用
Useless.
警察找不到他的
The police will never find him.
要么躲起来了 要么死了
Either he's in hiding or he's dead.
不管怎样 都得计划下一步怎么做
Either way,we have
to plan our next move.
什么事?
Yeah?
Hewes女士 一位客户代表来见你
Ms.Hewes,one of the client
reps is here to see you.
谁?
Who?
Peter Hassett
Peter hassett.
请他进来
Send him in.
你要跟他说什么?
What are you going to tell him?
事实
I'll tell him the truth.
没有Gregory Malina 我们会输
Without gregory malina,we're
going to lose the case.
Peter 请坐
Peter have a sit
Larry 过来一下 好吗?
Larry,come here for a second,will you?
Kevin!
Kevin,hey!
你早上有没有擦过
一辆卡迪拉克?
Hey,you ding up a caddy this morning?
我怎么了?
Did I what?
有人过来说 他的车门被刮花了
Got a guy in there saying
his door's all scratched up.
有没有?
Yes or no?
如果是我想到的那家伙
那些刮痕早就在了
If it's the guy I'm thinking
of,they may have been there before.
刷子该换了 Kevin
The brushes have to be replaced,kevin.
我早跟你说了
I've been telling you that.
不是刷子的问题 Larry
It's not the brushes,larry.
Manny擦的车没这种问题
Manny doesn't have these issues.
Wanda也没有
Neither does wanda.
Wanda穿的仔裤 都露屁股了
所以没人投诉她
Wanda wears jeans that let her patooty
show,is why nobody complains about her.
Manny刚被解雇
And manny just got fired.
Manny刚高中毕业
Manny just graduated high school.
他通知我了 回去上大学了
He gave notice and left for college.
是因为我太仔细吗?
Is this about me being more careful?
Larry 我没法再护着你
Larry,I can't keep covering for you.
这个节骨眼上
我都自身难保
At this point,my ass is on the line.
我不能再这样下去了
I gotta make a change.
你要解雇我?
You're firing me?
我女儿和你一起去的毕业舞会
还是我开车送的你们
My daughter went to prom with
you,I drove you there myself.
都是20年前的事了
That was 20 years ago.
我很想帮你的忙 但这样没用
明白?
Look,I tried to do you a favor
here,and it just didn't work out,okay?
把你的衣服交给Gloria
我会把这周的薪水付给你
Turn your shirt in to gloria,and
I'll pay you for the week.
对不起
I'm sorry.
Ellen?
什么事?
Yeah?
我给你父母打电话了
So I called your parents.
他们已经在路上
They were already on their way.
跟他们说了
我不能和他们吃午餐吗?
But you told them i couldn't have lunch.
- 没有
- 什么?
Uh,not really. What?
他们不愿取消午餐
Well,they wouldn't cancel.
好吧 以后如果我没空
你得负责和他们解释
Okay,in the future when I'm unavailable,you
just need to explain it to them.
说我在见客户 或者在开会
Say I'm with a client or in a meeting.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
我是该这么说的
I should have said that.
您找我?
Uh,you asked for me?
对 律师助理们已经为
证交备忘录做完注解了
Yeah,the paralegals have
finished annotating the sec memos.
我想要你检查一下 汇报给Tom
I'd like you to review
them and report to tom.
我该注意什么?
Uh,what am i looking for?
有矛盾的 任何显示异常的地方
Inconsistencies,anything
that even hints at a red flag.
帮我把文件取来 好吗?
Would you pull the files,please?
马上
Right away.
还有别的事吗?
Anything else?
你的新助理干得怎么样?
How's your new assistant working out?
有些小磕绊 会赶上步调的
It's a little bumpy,but he'll catch on.
我不喜欢他
I don't like him.
就这样 去工作吧
That's all. Get to work.
嘿! 你来了!
Hey! There he is!
Frobisher先生
Mr.Frobisher.
很高兴见到你 Larry
Good to see you,larry.
吃早餐吗? 来个煎蛋卷?
Hey,you need breakfast?
You want an omelet?
不要?
No?
这里有很棒的柠檬水
I'll tell you something,we
got some great lemonade here.
不 谢谢 Frobisher先生
No,thank you,mr.Frobisher.
请坐
Sit down,please.
我刚打完网拍墙球 很饿
I get famished after racquetball.
真锻炼身体
It's a great workout.
告诉你 比网球可刺激多了
A lot more exciting than
tennis,too,I'll tell you.
你打球吗?
You play?
保龄球
Bowling was my game.
是吗
Oh,yeah,yeah.
曾经在俱乐部比赛打出900分
Once hit a 900 series in league play.
自从眼睛不好之后 就没再打过了
But you know,i haven't been
out since my eyes started to go.
现在 我连一个二击全倒都打不到
These days,I couldn't even
pick up a two-pin spare.
没错
Exactly. Exactly.
很遗憾 我能为你做点什么?
So,sorry about that.
What can I do for you?
- 我想跟你开门见山 Frobisher先生
- 请讲
I'm going to be direct with
you,mr.Frobisher. Please.
我们有协议
We had a deal.
我知道
I know that.
我让雇员们投票同意你的和解方案
I got the employees to vote
for your settlement offer.
我努力让他们把Hewes女士解雇了
你让我做的我都做了
I tried to get 'em to fire mrs.
Hewes,I did everything you asked me to.
是的
Yes,you did.
你说过会给我好处
You said I'd be taken care of.
判决之后 会给你的
And after the trial,you will be.
那起码要一年 我等不了那么久
That could be a year from
now. I can't wait that long.
Larry 这个事情当初我说得很清楚
Larry,I was very clear about that.
你说要给我双倍报酬
You said you were going
to double our arrangement.
好吧 告诉你
All right,yeah,tell you what I'll do.
我会给手下打电话 好吗?
I'm gonna call my people,all right?
看看能不能帮你做点什么
We'll see if we can get
something set up for you here.
我交代的事 要同时进行 好吗?
In the meantime,keep doing
what you're doing,all right?
我们会熬过去...一起度过
We're gonna get through
this... together.
Ellen...他们来了
Ellen... they're here.
谁?
Who is?
你父母
Your parents.
- 她带了什么?
- 松饼
- What did she bring?
- Muffins.
我想是带给你的
I think they're for you.
亲爱的!
Honey!
我早就料到办公室很漂亮
但是 这好家伙!
I assumed the office was nice,but geez!
爸
Hi,dad. Hey.
我助理给你们打电话说
我不能去吃午饭了吗?
My assistant called,right,told
you I couldn't make lunch?
说了 我有些吃惊
不是你亲自打的
Yeah,I was a little surprised
you didn't call us yourself.
- 我们说好的
- 我知道
- We had a plan.
- I know.
- 我们这周晚点再约 我保证
- 好吧
- Let me make it up to you later
this week,I-I promise. - Yeah.
Ellen 我们得谈谈
Uh,ellen,we have to talk.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
我们出交通事故了
Uh... we were in a car accident.
天哪...你们没事吧?
Oh,my G... are you okay?
一个月之前的事了 我们没事
It was a month ago. We're fine.
撞了一个横穿马路的保安
But,uh,I hit a crossing guard.
在学校外面
Outside a school.
他受伤了吗?
Oh... um... was he hurt?
她 叫Linda Reynolds
She. Linda reynolds.
Linda的臀部受伤了
Linda broke her hip.
她在哈德森综合医院做了手术
She had surgery at hudson general.
- 什么时候?
- 两周前
When? Two weeks ago.
他不让我给你电话
Uh... he wouldn't let me call you.
你很忙 我不想你担心
You're busy. I-I didn't
want you to worry.
我们有保险
We have insurance.
我和公司的律师见过面
I,uh... I met with the
lawyer from the company.
然后?
And?
他们真是群混蛋
These guys are sleazeballs.
那女保安在医院呢
但他们考虑的只是赔钱的额度
Lady's in the hospital,all
they care about is bottom line.
爸 律师怎么说?
Dad,what did the lawyer say?
我们会处理好的
I've got it under control.
我明天下午上庭
My deposition is tomorrow afternoon.
明天?
Tomorrow?
我跟他说过
I told him.
你女儿是个出色的律师...
跟她谈谈
Your daughter's a successful
attorney-- talk to her.
会搞定的 Denise
It's under control,denise.
好吧 告诉我怎么回事
Okay,just tell me what happened.
我们去你姐姐家 我取笑你姐夫
We were headed to your sister's,I
made a crack about your brother-in-law,
你妈很生气
and your mother got angry.
这和那事儿有什么关系?
What does that have to do with it?
撞到保安的时候 我们正在吵架
We were arguing when i hit the guard.
那是我的错?
So it's my fault?
- 不 我是说我们正在吵架...
- Ellen?
- No,I'm just saying we were fighting...
也许因为这个...
...And maybe that's why I...
Patty找你
Um,patty wants to see you.
这事儿我还得跟你们聊聊
等一会 好吗?
I want to talk about this
more,so just-just wait here,okay?
我们得去医院
We have to go to the hospital.
干吗?
What for?
去看望她
To say hello.
我告诉Linda我们会顺路看她
I told linda we'd stop by.
- 你妈做了松饼
- 不
- Your mother made muffins.
- No.No,no.
别给她任何东西
You don't give her anything.
我回来给你解释
I'll explain when I get back.
拜托 就在我办公室等我
Please,just wait in my office.
我的天!
Aw,for crying out loud.
Hewes女士
我真不知道怎样才能赢官司
You know... I just don't understand
how we could win at trial,mrs.Hewes,
除非你有什么对我们隐瞒
unless you got something
you're not telling us.
真相是 我们可能都闹不上法庭
The truth is,we may never get to trial.
那你搞什么?
Then what the hell are you doing?
Larry 我没法想像这些天
你承受多大压力
Larry,I can't imagine the pressure
you must be under these days.
不 你理解不了
No. You can'T.
你为Frobisher先生工作多久了?
How many years did you
work for mr.Frobisher?
打从你女儿Glory出生
你就为他工作了34年
没错
That's right.
结果却落得这个下场
And nothing to show for it.
像这样的诉讼案
我们每采取一项行动都是有目的的
In a litigation like this,every
move we make has a purpose.
要求开庭也是我们获得
更好和解条件的手段
Pushing for a trial is also how
we get a higher settlement offer.
那你愿意和解
So you'd be willing to settle.
我不想
Well,I-I don't want to.
但如果Frobisher的人给出公平条件
But if frobisher's people
came up with a fair offer,
我得建议你们认真考虑一下
I'd have to advise you all
to seriously consider it.
怎么个公平法?
What's fair?
既然找不到Gregory Malina
我想拿到...
After losing gregory
malina,I'd like to go in at...
3.5到4亿
$350,$400 million.
要谈判 但在这点上
But it's a negotiation,and
at this point,
我们有可能只能拿到1.75亿
we might have to
accept as little as 175.
1.75亿?
175?
那只是最坏打算
Only as a last resort.
有道理
Makes sense.
Larry 我需要你支持我们的工作
In the meantime,larry,I need you
to be supportive of our efforts.
Patty愿意和解?
Patty's willing to settle now.
我觉得不会
I doubt it.
Popler老煽动客户代表摇摆不定
Popler has got a lot of
sway with the client reps.
我想她只是要拉拢他
I'm sure she's just
trying to get him on board.
你没解雇他?
You didn't fire him yet?
为什么要炒他?
Why would I do that?
Patty想让你这么做
Well,patty wants you to.
她没说
She didn't say that.
她说她不喜欢他
She said she didn't like him.
那表示...?
And that means...?
开了他
Get rid of him.
证券交易的文件?
Sec files?
对
Yes.Yep.
这里
This is... it.
1998之后的文件都拿来了?
You brought me everything from 1998?
1998?
我需要从证券交易调查初始
到现在的所有文件
Yeah,I need everything from the
beginning of the sec investigation.
不只是庭审相关的
Not just the trial.
对不起
Sorry.
我父母去哪里了?
Where did my parents go?
你爸说起医院里的女人 所以...
Your dad said something about
a woman in the hospital,so...
Parsons! 过来
Parsons!Let's go.
你律师来了
Your attorney's here.
转身 面对墙 把手放背后
Turn around and face the wall.
Put your hands behind your back.
然后你就可以进行申辩
And then you'll enter your plea.
联系我父母了吗?
Did you contact my parents?
他们在赶过来
They're on their way.
Patty呢?
And patty?
我们找不到她
We can't find her.
不过我们还在跟踪Tom Shayes
But we're still watching tom shayes.
Ellen Parsons
Ellen parsons.
6% 坡度 快果岭
高球洞右侧推杆
Six-percent grade,fast
greens,breaks to the left.
要全神贯注
It's all about focus and concentration.
我也希望这案子 能跟你打高尔夫一样
用短杆策略快速搞定
As much as I wish this case could
be decided by your short game,
我还是为你准备了上庭的资料
we've got a deposition
to prepare you for.
我看过了你在政府审讯时的证词
I've gone through your transcripts
from the government trial,
有些地方...我觉得可以做得更好
and there are a couple of areas...
I feel we can handle better.
你觉得我说得太多?
You think I gave away too much?
我想介绍个专家
负责帮你准备上庭作证的事
I'd like to bring in a specialist,help
prepare you for the deposition.
Patty Hewes现在就专注这一个案子
要把你扳倒
Patty hewes's whole case
now is about tripping you up.
去做吧
Let's do it.
弄个强悍点的
找个最强硬的律师
Get us a barracuda. Get us the toughest
son-of-a-btich attorney you can find.
不过告诉你 Ray
But I'm telling you something,ray.
她怕了 哥们
She's scared,man.
她已经没信心了
She's losing her confidence.
你怎么这么想?
What makes you think so?
我有可靠消息透露她想和解
I have it on good authority
that she's willing to settle.
所谓的可靠消息是谁说的?
Whose authority?
只要花1.75亿
$175 million is what it would cost.
几个星期前
这女人还团结一心要开庭 对吗?
A few weeks ago,this woman
was,like,gung ho for a trial,right?
她怕了 哥们
She's scared,man.
你说 可靠消息 什么意思?
What do you mean,on good authority?
不 别担心 只是...
No,don't worry about it.It's just...
天哪 不
Jesus,no.
什么?
What?
Art? Art?
别告诉我 你和内部的人有联系
Don't tell me you've been
talking to someone on the inside.
听着 他 呃...他人不错 Ray
Look,he's A... he's a good guy,ray.
是个直性子
He's a straight shooter.
你知道的 其实我们该感激他
You know something,we should
be showing him some gratitude.
真的 我希望你
嗯...给他建个账户
Seriously,I want you to,you know,get
him set up with some account,you know?
海外账户或什么的
Uh,offshore,however we do that.
绝对不行
Absolutely not!
有谁知道这事?
Who knows about this?
没人
No one.
你没给他钱吧?
You haven't paid him anything,have you?
我向他保证过我会的 Ray
I gave him my word,ray.
好吧 不管任何情况 我告诉你...
All right,in no uncertain
terms,I am telling you...
别再跟他接触
to shut this down!
无论在何种情况下
永远不许再跟他联系
Never again are you to have contact
with this man,under any circumstances!
Authur 你可能会因此进监狱的
Arthur... you can go to jail for this.
明白吗?
You understand?
别再联系了
No more.
好吧
All right.
我知道了
I understand.
1.75亿?
175?
噢 真是幅美丽的画卷
Well,isn't this a swell picture.
什么事 Ray
What,ray?
你的小宝贝不拉屎吗
Your little precious never takes a shit?
真希望在你心情好点的时候碰到你
I wish i caught you in a better mood.
我没事
I'm fine.
或许你能收敛下脾气
私下听我说两句
Well,then perhaps you'd care to
humor me for a moment,off the record.
洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
请理解 我没被授权
Understand,I'm not authorized.
不能做任何保证
I'm making no promises.
我不会要你保证什么
I'm not taking any.
我的委托人撤回了1亿赔偿和解
My client pulled his
offer of a hundred million.
如果我让他重新考虑 增加价码
你说怎么样?
What if I could get him to
reconsider,maybe even sweeten the pot a bit?
他有什么必要那么做
Why would he do that?
-我们来算算这笔数 Patty
-好的
- Let's you and I do the math here,patty.
- 'Kay.
你那边的情况是
All right,here's what you've got.
有个亿万富翁 不论事实与否
人们都认为他贪污
A billionaire who the public already
believes is corrupt,whether he is or isn'T.
他根本就是
He is.
我这边的情况是
And here's what I got.
没有必杀目击证人或其它有力的证据
能证明我的委托人确实做错了事
No smoking-gun witness or any credible
evidence that my client did anything wrong.
你确定吗
You're sure about that?
这样下去是个僵局 Patty
你我都心知肚明
It's a draw,patty,and we both know it.
现在如果我们法庭上见
谁都没把握胜
Now,we go in that courtroom,we
might as well flip a coin.
俩旧相识之间一定要弄成这样吗？
Is that any way for two
old friends to do business?
你们开价多少
What's your number?
我不敢保证有2亿那么多
但...
Well,I'm not saying i could
go as high as 200,but...
大概到底多少?
But in the ballpark?
我们先口头商量 我觉得1.5亿
Oh,we're just talking
here,but I think 150...
大概能让你满意
would probably get you a deal.
或者 1.75亿
Maybe even... 175.
- 怎么
- Larry这事我说对了吗
- So...
- Was I right about larry?
是的 Peter
Yes,peter.
Popler先生泄露情报给
Frobisher团伙
Mr.Popler's leaking
information to frobisher's camp.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
我告诉他和解赔偿约在1.75亿
I gave him 175 as a settlement number.
Ray Fiske马上给我开同样的价
Ray fiske brought it right back to me.
那你打算怎么办
So what are you going to do?
可惜我们不能以此作为
对付Frobisher的证据
Unfortunately,we don't have the
evidence to use this against frobisher.
没有书面上的记录
没有金钱交易
There won't be a paper
trail,money exchanged.
我觉得现在最好不采取任何行动
I think the best thing to
do right now is nothing.
继续盯着Larry
We'll keep an eye on larry.
同时 向其他委托人保密
In the meantime,let's not mention
this to the other client reps.
自从Gregory Malina未出现作证
我们的调查员一直在找他
Our investigators are trying to locate gregory
malina since he skipped out on his deposition.
但Malina先生好像蒸发了一般
Unfortunately,mr.Malina
seems to have disappeared.
就这些吗
So that's it?
我们拿不到他的证词?
We don't have his testimony?
Larry 别着急 让他们说完
Relax,larry. Just let them talk.
当然我们仍在找他
Of course,we're still looking for him,
不过一旦某人离开本州...
but once someone leaves the state...
这个证人怎么会就这么消失了?
How the hell does a witness
just up and disappear?
我觉得你该明白我们要对付的是谁
I think you all should
know what we're up against.
我们有理由相信 在Malina先生作证前
他的人身安全就受到威胁
We have reason to believe that mr.Malina's
life was threatened prior to the deposition.
很可能是控方的人找到了他
It's quite possible that
the other side got to him.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
他被杀了?
He's been killed?
我们正就此可能性进行调查 是的
We're seriously looking
into that possibility,yes.
您现在进入的是Arther Frobisher
先生的语音信箱 请留言 并祝您一天愉快
**********
这整个星期我都在给你留言
回我电话
I've been leaving messages
all week.Call me back.
我们得开始打算
We got to get going here.
记得回电话
So,call me back.
Larry 晚餐好了
Larry,dinner's ready.
你认为他们杀了Gregory
You think they killed this gregory guy?
我们不知道
We don't know.
他再也没打过Katie电话 对吧
He never tried to call
katie again,did he?
是的
No.
打过一次
No,just that once.
- Ellen 如果这是真的...
- 我知道
- Ellen,if this is true...
- I know.
谢谢你们能来 我很感激
Thank you guys for showing
up. I appreciate that.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
哦 天哪 载我回家 伙计
Oh,boy.Take me home,man.
你杀了那个孩子吗
Did you kill that kid?
什么
What?
你到底是个什么人?
What kind of man are you?
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
那个证人 Gregory Malina
Patty Hewes说他被人除掉了
That witness-- gregory malina--
patty hewes says he was knocked off.
哦 我的老天爷
Oh,for christ's sake.
我究竟得告诉你多少次 Larry
那个女人是疯子
How many times I got to tell
you,that woman is crazy,larry.
我...我根本不知道你在说什么
I don'T... I don't know
what you're talking about.
我不认识什么Gregory Malina
I don't know any gregory malina.
你到底什么毛病
What's the matter with you?
我给你打了一星期的电话
I've been calling you all week.
得了 冷静点 行吗
All right,just relax,will you?
很晚了 我们明天再谈好吗
It's late. Can't we do
this tomorrow,please?
我得要我的钱
I need my money!
- 先生 请你退后
- 嘿 Derek Derek Derek 没关系
- Sir,I need you to stand back.
- Hey,derek,derek,derek,come on. Hey,derek,derek,derek,come on.
不要紧 Larry是我的朋友
这边来
Hey,it's all right.Larry's a
friend of mine.Come here,come here.
你现在不会希望我给你什么钱
You don't want me to give
you any money right now.
相信我
Trust me.
现在为止
我们俩都没做过什么违法的事
So far neither of us has
done anything illegal.
你答应过我
You gave me your word.
听好了
Listen to me,will you?
给你钱就是犯罪 明白吗
Giving you money is a crime,all right?
这是行贿受贿 妨碍司法程序
It's bribery,obstruction of justice.
我们俩都会进监狱的
We could both go to jail.
别这样
Come on.
对我们来说就这样最好
It's the best way for
both of us. All right?
嘿 到这来
Hey,come here.
你住在泽西 对吗
You live in jersey,right?
给他20块
Give him a 20,will you?
为你自己好
你还是打个车回家吧 去吧
Just do yourself a favor-- get
a cab and go home,please.Come on.
Patty Hewes也长耳朵
Patty hewes has ears,too.
也许我找错了人
Maybe I'm talking to the wrong person.
Larry 别想威胁我
Larry,you don't want to threaten me.
拿上钱
Take the money.
我给你抹过地板 你这个婊子养的
I mopped your floors,you son of a bitch!
哦 该死的
Oh,shit.
替你清扫了34年的垃圾!
34 years I cleaned your shit.
你在干吗 别那么粗鲁 伙计
What are you doing? Be gentle here,man.
你下地狱去吧
I hope you burn in hell!
哦 上帝...喂 是我
Oh,for chri... yeah,it's me.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
我们不辞而别 很是抱歉
I'm sorry we had to run off like that.
我很钦佩你 挂住探望这个女士
Dad,I admire you wanting
to visit this woman,
但从法律的角度考虑
这不是妙招
but legally it was not a good move.
这不是什么招
It wasn't a move.
我知道
I get it.
但想给她送松饼这这种事会被对方利用
反将你一军
But bringing her muffins,that kind
of thing can be used against you.
这等于间接承认自己有罪
It's an admission of guilt.
我开车撞了她
I hit the woman with my car.
我把她送到医院
I sent her to the hospital.
难道我就不该去探望她吗
I'm not supposed to go visit her?
不幸的是 不能
Unfortunately,no.
你也不能认错
And you can't apologize,either.
你卷入了一起官司
You're involved in a lawsuit.
你得明哲保身
You have to protect yourself.
妈妈 知道吗 我不饿
Mom,you know what? I'm not hungry.
胡说
Nonsense.
Ellen 我见过那个女人
Ellen,I met the woman.
我亲眼看到
I looked her in the eye.
在未来的2年里
她都要接受物理治疗
She's going to need physical
therapy for the next two years.
你并不需要为她买单
It's not your job to get her bills paid.
这是她律师该操心的事
It's her lawyer'S.
我并不觉得她的律师
比保险公司的推销员更可靠
Well,I don't trust her lawyer any more than
I trust the guy from the insurance company.
对他们来说 不过是个游戏
It's all a game to them.
是的
Yes,it is.
你可能会输了这场游戏
And you could lose.
这就是在这次庭证中
你得保证回答简短
That is why,in this deposition,you
have to keep your answers brief.
- 别添油加醋
- 好吧
- Do not elaborate.
- Fine.
简单点
Keep it simple.
坚持事实 那个女人站在哪儿
你当时开多快
Stick to the facts-- where the woman
was standing,how fast you were driving.
类似这些 知道吗
That kind of thing. Understand?
知道了
Yeah,got it.
我觉得我应该陪着你
I think I should be there with you.
不需要
Not necessary.
Gary 她已经不是12岁了
她是个律师
Gary,she's not a 12-year-old
anymore; she's a lawyer.
让她帮助你
Let her help you.
她还要上班
She has to be at work.
不是吗
Don't you?
我会抽时间的 我会去的
I'll make time. I'll be there.
噢 这里看起来是块不毛之地啊
Well... this looks like
a whole lot of nothing.
你知道谁本州的
这块地是谁建起来的吗
You know who built up
this part of the state?
黄蜂
Wasps.
海狸
Beavers.
没明白你的意思
You lost me.
真的 我没玩笑
No,I'm not kidding.
以前这里满是海狸
Place was flush with them.
印第安人捕获海狸
拿它们来交易
Indians used to trap them and
then trade them for everything--
换来毛毯 短柄斧 铁壶
blankets,hatchets,iron kettles.
之后他们看上了白人的货物
Then when they got hooked
on the white man's goods,
他们开始拿他们仅剩的物品来交易
they started trading the only
other thing they had left.
水獭皮?
Otters?
不 傻瓜 是土地
No,you idiot.Land.
我想把这里开发出来
I'm going to develop this.
房地产可不是你擅长的生意
Real estate-- that's
not your thing.
我早已厌倦像这样隔岸观火
知道吗
I'm sick and tired of standing around
the sidelines like this,you know?
我得 我得建造出个名堂来
I need to... I need to build something.
你想告诉我Gregory Malina
现在怎么样了吗?
You want to tell me what
happened to gregory malina?
别问我 问Ray Fiske
Don't ask me; ask ray fiske.
问的时候 别忘了问他
当初他是怎么认识他的
And while you're at it,ask him how
he knows malina in the first place,
并问他为什么在棕榈海滩
让他弄了间公寓?
and why he used him to set
up the condo in palm beach.
问这些又能怎样?
What difference does that make?
我不信任他
I don't trust him.
五年前 为了你我铤而走险
Five years ago,I went
out on a limb for you.
身处险境的人不只你一个
You're not the only one in
the line of fire here,arthur.
Gregory Malina现在怎么样了
What happened to gregory malina?
看来我们的小Gregory Malina
终究都要出庭作证
Looks like our boy gregory malina's
going to be deposed after all.
确保这次不要失手
Make sure it doesn't
get screwed up this time.
我亲自出马
I'll do it myself.
我以为你不想知道
I thought you didn't want to know.
我现在想知道
I do now.
喔 抱歉
Ooh,excuse me. Sorry.
- 他叫什么
- Theo
- What's his name?
- Theo.
Hewes女士 之前在你办公室里时
Um,ms.Hewes,when we were in your office,
你是在暗示我应该开除他吗?
were you suggesting
that I should fire him?
为什么这么问?
Why?
你想开除他吗?
You want to fire him?
他刚开始这份工作
我想应该再给他点时间
He just started. I thought
I should give him some time.
他是你的助理 你看着办
He's your assistant. Do what you want.
发现什么了吗?
Anything jumping out at you?
还没有
Not yet.
证券交易监委有个官员一直死咬
着Frobisher的公司不放
There is an official from the sec who was very
aggressive in going after frobisher's company.
Tom跟我都认为该跟他谈谈
Tom and I thought he
might be worth talking to.
是谁?
His name?
George Moore
George moore.
我想他那没什么线索
I don't think there's anything there.
政府公诉的时候
Moore被询问过多次
Moore was interviewed extensively
for the government trial.
我们就想听听他的意见
I thought we'd just pick his brain.
如果Tom觉得这有用 我没意见
If tom thinks it's
useful,it's fine with me.
Hewes女士
明天我可以外出一会吗?
Uh,ms.Hewes,is it okay if tomorrow
I step out for a few hours?
要干吗?
What for?
我父亲开车撞伤了个女人
My father hit a woman with his car.
法庭传唤他出庭作证
我想我最好陪着他
He's being deposed,and i
thought that I should be there.
当然可以
Well,of course.
是他的责任吗?
Is he at fault?
他是这么认为的
He seems to think so.
我是说 他是那种愿意负责的人
I mean,he's the kind of guy who
likes to take responsibility.
最好当心
Better be careful.
原告可能会很恶毒
We plaintiff attorneys can be vicious.
最好的辩护策略就是怪罪受害人
His best strategy is
to blame the victim.
我知道
I know.
不计代价 都是受害人的错
就这样
At all costs. It was her fault,period.
他在浴室 马上就出来
He's in the bathroom,but
he'll be back in a minute.
很抱歉打扰你们吃晚饭了
I'm so sorry to interrupt your dinner.
噢...
Oh...
你好 你肯定是Chloe
Hello.You must be chloe.
我是Patty Hewes
Patty hewes.
你是Rob吧 你好
And rob. Hello.
你来这干吗?
What are you doing here?
刚好来这附近
I was in the neighborhood.
就想过来见见你的家人
Thought I'd meet the family.
现在不方便
Now is not a good time.
明早我去你办公室吧?
How about I come by the office tomorrow?
等不到那时了 Larry
Ah,afraid it can't wait,larry.
Ray Fiske来见过我
Ray fiske came to see me.
他提出了一项和解协议
He offered a settlement.
太好了
Hey,that's terrific.
1.75亿
$175 million.
我们该接受吗?
Should we take it?
干吗问我?
Why are you asking me?
因为1.75亿是一个...有趣的数
Because 175 is A... interesting number.
我不知道你在暗示什么
I don't know what you're implying.
你一直跟他们私下来往
You've been talking to the other side.
你疯了吗?
Are you nuts?
不 你最好别说话
No,you don't want to do that.
刑事律师不在场
你最好保持沉默
Don't speak without a
criminal attorney present.
你已经要做3到5年的牢了
You're already facing three to five.
你怎么敢跑来我家指控我?
How dare you come in here and
hijack me with accusations?
是的 Larry 其实我挺喜欢你
但我觉得你自身难保
Yeah,the truth is,larry,I like you,but
I think you're in over your head,
而且你不该去坐牢
and prison is the last
place where you belong.
Arthur Frobisher很聪明
Arthur frobisher is smart.
我相信他用某种手段
侵占了你的血汗钱
I'm sure he's got a way to
get you your blood money,
而且没留下丝毫文书痕迹
所以我来是向你许诺
with no paper trail,so I'm really just
here tonight to make you a promise.
是吗? 许诺什么?
Oh,yeah? What's that?
我会一直盯着...
直到你用钱买房子
I'm going to wait and
watch... until you buy a house,
或Mildred买车
甚至是Chloe买牙刷
or mildred buys a car,or
chloe here buys a toothbrush.
你要搞清楚 Larry
You need to understand this,larry,
只要你家有人敢花这笔
钱的一分一毫
no popler for the next hundred years will
be able to spend a nickel of that money
都会被人羞辱 丢尽面子
并面临牢狱之灾
without being
humiliated,disgraced and locked up.
祝你们有个愉快的晚上
You all have a nice night.
辩方如何申辩?
How do you plea?
无罪
Not guilty.
被告没有潜逃可能 法官大人
Not a flight risk,your honor.
之前没有犯罪记录
No prior criminal record.
是守法良民
An upstanding member of the community.
保释金定为150万美元
Bail is set at $1.5 million.
下一个
Next.
你愿意起誓说出真相 全部真相
Do you swear to tell the
truth,the whole truth,
绝无谎言吗?
and nothing but the
truth,so help you god?
我愿意
I do.
注意到停车标志停下时
你看到Reynolds小姐了吗?
And when you pulled even with the
stop sign,did you see miss reynolds?
看到了
Uh,yes.
她在我左手边 大概离我10尺远
She was standing to my
left,about ten feet away.
你看到Reynolds
小姐朝你的车走来吗?
Did you see miss reynolds
walk towards your vehicle?
没有
No.
一点都没瞟见?
Not even out of the corner of your eye?
继续 你已经说过没有了
Move on. You already said no.
Parsons先生...
Mr.Parsons...
发生车祸时你的心情如何?
what was your general state of
mind leading up to the accident?
你能说清楚点吗?
How about being a little more specific?
你当时是否沮丧? 生气?
Were you upset? Angry?
车祸发生前 我跟我太太...
Uh,well,just before it
happened,my wife and I...
能休息5分钟吗?
May we take five minutes,please?
Parsons先生 我告诉过你
Mr.Parsons,I told you before,
你不用告诉别人你当时
情绪如何或你注意力是否在别处
no one needs to know your emotional state
or that your attention was somewhere else.
我当时正跟我太太争吵
我说的是事实
My wife and I were arguing.
I'm telling them what happened.
- 作为你的律师 我要告诉你...
- 你不是他的律师
- And as your attorney,I'm telling you...
- You're not his attorney.
你代表的是他的保险公司
You represent his insurance company.
我想跟父亲单独谈谈
I'd like a moment with my father.
爸爸 他是对的
Dad,he's right.
你跟那个混蛋意见一致?
You agree with that creep?
你的保险条款只会负担20万
Your policy only covers $200,000.
- 如果原告胜诉...
- 她有名字的
If the plaintiff is
awarded... She has a name--
Linda Reynolds
linda reynolds.
如果你承认有错而她获赔超过20万
那你就得自己负担那笔钱
If you admit fault and she's awarded more
than $200,000,you're personally liable.
本来就是我的错
It was my fault.
这是起事故
It was an accident.
如果是工作 你就走吧
If that's work,you should go.
那个律师反正都不是在为我争取
Look,this guy isn't even
fighting for me anyway.
他只不过要想拒付Linda
的医疗费用为保险公司省钱
He's just trying to save his company money
by refusing to pay linda's medical expenses.
我为什么要帮他呢?
Why should I help him?
因为她的律师会
争取尽可能多的赔偿
Because she's got a lawyer who's
going to go after every penny he can.
所以你认为我该撒谎?
So you're saying i should
just go in there and lie?
我认为他们会撒谎
I'm saying that they will.
他们会职责你有重大过失
They'll spin into gross negligence.
这个世界很现实 爸爸
This is the real world,dad.
我不用你教我什么是现实世界
Hey,I don't need you to
teach me about the real world.
我发了誓
I swore under oath.
你是律师 Ellen
你告诉我怎么做
But you're the
lawyer,ellen,tell me what to do.
我跟你说了很多次了
I've told you what
to do again and again.
Parsons先生
发生车祸时你的心情如何?
Mr.Parsons,what was your general state
of mind leading up to the accident?
谢谢你肯见我
Thank you for seeing me again.
感谢你来电 Larry
Well,thank you for calling,larry.
那晚的事让我很不舒服
I was sick about the other night.
发生的一切很糟糕
That was a terrible thing that happened.
我该向你道歉
Nah,I should apologize to you.
我压力很大
It's just I got all these pressures.
我明白
I get it,I get it.
Larry 事实上
我的律师反对我跟你接触
Larry,the truth is,my attorney
doesn't even want me talking to you,
所以直到审判结束以后
我才能补偿你
so I'm not going to be able to
make good until after the trial.
我理解 我能等等
你别忘了就行
I understand,and i can hold
out. Just don't forget about me.
拜托了... 记住我那份
Please... don't cut me out.
还有 证人的那件事?
Oh,that other thing,the witness?
我正在调查中
I'm looking into it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你知道你让我想起谁?
You know who you remind me of,don't you?
我父亲
My dad.
这对我来说意义非凡
That means a lot.
是你这样的人造就了这个伟大的国家
Guys like you are what make
this country great,larry.
证券交易监委的人要提前会议
你能十分钟后准备好吗?
The guy from the sec wants to push
up our meeting. You ready in ten?
可以的
Sure.
妈 发生了什么事?怎么回事?
Mom. What happened?What's going on?
你爸爸不愿意给你打电话
但我想你应该知道
Your father wouldn't call
you,but I thought you should know.
知道什么?
Know what?
他们不光要我们负责医疗费用
They're not just suing us
for hospital bills anymore.
没事的
It's okay.
他们说那个女人的伤比想象的严重
她以后都无法工作了
They're saying this woman's hurt worse then
they thought,and she may never work again.
他们要多少钱?
How much are they asking for?
超过100万
Over a million dollars.
他们不能这样做 是吗?
They can't do that,can they?
我是说 不能就这么
认定我们欠她那么多钱
I mean,they can't just say
we owe them all that money.
妈妈 他们可以的
Yeah,mom,they can.
你爸爸没必要说出我们吵架的事
Your father didn't have to
tell them we were arguing.
Ellen? 车来了
Ellen? Uh,car's here.
你妈妈之前来电话了
Your mom called earlier.
我只是... 是我的错
I just... it's my fault.
我没找到机会...早点告诉你
I didn't have a chance
to... tell you earlier.
没关系
It's fine.
你知道吗?
You know what?
有关系 你被开除了
It's not fine. You're fired.
他们要带她去哪?
Where are they taking her?
Rikers岛
Rikers island.
我的天啊
Oh,my god.
保释要多少钱?
150万美金
What will it cost to post bond?
我们负不起啊
合解以后没那么多钱了
We can't afford that.*******
他是想扳倒Frobisher的
调查员之一
He was a lead investigator who
tried to take down frobisher.
真的吗?
really?
我们要找Moore先生
We're looking for mr.Moore.
你好
Hello there.
我是Tom Shayes
Oh,tom shayes.
我是Ellen Parsons
Ellen parsons.
见到你们很高兴
来 请坐
The pleasure's mine.
Come on in.Take a seat.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好
Hello
Larry 有时间吗?
Hey,larry,you got a second?
我想... 我想再跟你保证一次
关于那个证人的事...
Listen,I want to... I want to reassure
you that that thing with the witness...
我查过了 我以个人名义担保
Gregory Malina很安全
I looked into it,and I can personally
guarantee you that gregory malina is safe.
听到这个消息我很高兴
I'm glad to hear that.
出于一些私人原因
所以他不愿出庭作证--
Yeah,evidently he had his own
reasons for not wanting to testify--
好像是跟毒品有关
drugs or something like that.
我不该指责你
I shouldn't have accused you.
没关系
No,it all right.
好吧 我稍后跟你联系
All right,I'll talk to you later.
他说Gregory Malina还活着
He says gregory malina is alive.
你相信吗?
Do you believe him?
你呢?
Do you?
我们会查到的
Well,we're going to find out.
我很高兴我们能达成协议 Larry
I'm glad you and I could
come to an arrangement,larry.
我也是
Me,too.
为了弥补过失要我做什么都行
Whatever I could do
to make things right.
请不要这样
Please don't do this.
你现在决定 你要我们在一起
还是要这份工作?
You decide right now-- do you
want us or do you want this job?
现...在!
Right... now!
我们结束了 Ellen
We're done,ellen.
是我 我很抱歉
Hey,it's me.I'm so sorry.
拜托你...打个电话给我好吗?
Just please... call me back,okay?
-------------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
-------------------------------
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
-=YTET-伊甸园&CHD联盟字幕组=-
时间轴: 咔肉肉 调整 捕头@CHD联盟
翻译: elise 小乔 silvierun
校对: sade
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync:咔肉肉